Guide to the Leonid N. Stolovich papers M1624
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Correspondence
  - Family members
    - Letters to Leonid Stolovich and his family (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence
    - "A": Abashina-Melts, Nelli; Abramenko, G.A.; Adams, Valmar; Aksenova, Asia; Akulov, Valentin, L. (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - "A": Aleksakhina, Irina V.; Aliev, Geogii M.; Altshuller, Mark G. (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - "A": Aliev, G. M. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - "A": Amurskii, Vitalii; Andrijauskas, Antanas; Anikst, A.A.; Apresian, G.Z.; Apushkin, Boris; Ariste, P. (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - "A": Antonovich, A. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - "A": Arlandi, Gian Franco (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - "A": Arkhangelskii, L.M.; Aronchik, Isaak L.; Aseev, Iu.A.; Aslamov, Aslan; Asmolova, V.; Asmus, V.F. (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - "B": Babushkin; Bakos, Oliver; Bakshtanovskii, Vladimir I.; Barsheva, Irina; Barskaia, Liudmia; Basin, E.; Baruzdin, S.A.; Bashmakova, Nataliia; Bassel, Naftali; Batiushkova, A.S. (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - "B": Babushkin, S. A. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - "B": Becker, Jakob; Belavenets, N.S.; Belyi, O.V.; Berestnevy, Klara i Vl.F. (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - "B": Belik, A.P.; Bernshtein, B.M.; Bersa, Gabriele (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - "B": Bezmozdin, L.N.; Bilinskis, Iakov S.; Bliakher, E.D.; Blium, R.N.; Bliumkin, Vl.A.; Bobyshev, D.; Bodsch, Vera; Bormane, D. (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - "B": Berestnev, Vladimir F. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - "B": Bernshtein, Boris M. (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - "B": Bernshtein, Boris M. (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - "B": Borev, Iurii B. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - "B": Borev, Iurii B. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - "B": Borev, Iurii B. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - "B": Borisov, Georgii Iu.; Borodin, Evgenii; Botvinnik, Nataliia M.; Brandt, G.; Bronshtein, M.L. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - "B": Briazu, M. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - "B": Brozik, Vl.; Brunius, Teddy; Burov, Aleksandr I.; Burov, V.G.; Byckling, Liisa; Bykov, R.A.; Bychkov, V. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - "B": Bubelets, Marina (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - "C": Chavchavadze, M.Z.; Cherednichenko, Tatiana; Cherniak, Irma; Chertin, IU.N.; Chunaev, S.; Chukhina, L.A. (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - "C": Chvatik, K. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - "C": Culbrik, Svetozar (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - "D": Damnjanovic, Milan (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - "D": Dano, Juraj; Dmitrieva, N.A.; Dneprov (Reznik); Dobromirov, Vl.D.; Dribzo, Abram D.; Drobnitskii, O.; Druzhnikov, IU.I.; Dubin, G.; Dubchenko, V.S. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - "D": Davidovich, Vsevolod Ev.; Davies, Richard D. (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - "D": Dziemidok, Bohdan (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - "E": Egorov, Boris F. (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - "E": Egorov, A.G.; Eigorn, N.; Elshtein, Alla; Elshtein, Natan; Emelianov, Boris Vl; Ermolaeva, L.P.; Etkind, Aleksandr; Epstein, Mikhail; Erhard, John (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - "E": Ender, A. G. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - "E": Eremeev, A.F. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "E": Erhard, John (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - "F": Farbshtein, Aleksandr A. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - "F": Feldmann, Arnold; Fischerova, Anna (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - "F": Firsov, Boris M. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - "F": Fisherova, Anna (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - "F": Farbshtein, A.A.; Fidelman, Zinaida Vl.; Florenskii, Pavel V.; Fokin, S.; Frablina, Elena M., Frosh, Tatiana; Fish, T. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - "F": Funke, Gerhard (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - "G": Gabinskii, M.A.; Gavrilov, Boris; Gasparov, B.M.; Ganzen, Liudmila L.; Gasparov, M.L.; Galeev, Bulat; Gachev, G.D.; Genzer, L.N.; Genis, Al. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - "G": Gaidenko, Piama P. and Davydov, Iurii N.; Garai, Laszlo; Gellner, Ernest; Gens, Leo; Genis, Alexandr; Golaszewska, M.; Goldberg, Vladislav (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - "G": Garai, Laszlo (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - "G": Gerobnik, Genadii I.; Gilin, Efim; Glazman, M.S.; Glushkovskaia, L.F.; Golubev, Boris; Goncharenko, N. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - "G": Goldentrikht, Semen S. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - "G": Goranov, Kr. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - "G": Goranov, Kr.; Gorbunov, Nikolai; Gribachev, N.; Grinishin, D.M.; Gulyga, Arsenii V. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - "G": Grableva, Alla (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - "G": Gugenhan-Speisei, E. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - "G": Gulyga, Arsenii V. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - "G": Gurenko, E.G.; Gurevich, A.Ia.; Gurevich, A.M.; Gushchin, Dmitrii Al.; Gushchina, V. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - "H": Hagemeister, Michael; Hainsalu, Lehte; Herber, Christa; Hermeren, Goran (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - "H": Hermeren, Goran (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - "H": Hones, Waltrant (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - "I": Iadov, Vl.A.; Iakobson, P.M.; Iakovlev, Ev.; Iastrebova, N.; Iudelevich, M.A. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - "I": IAkovlev, Evgenii G. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - "I": Ianosi, Ion; Ilves, Toomas Hendrik; Ird, Kaarel (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - "I": Iliadi, Aleksandr N. (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - "I": Iurovskaia (Rogova), Elga (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - "I": IUrovskaia, Elga P. (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - "I": Ivanov, Vl.; Ivanova (Pallo), Liudmila V.; Ivanko, L.I.; Islamova, Lilia A.; Ikonnikova, Irina; Isakov, Sergei G. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - "J": Jasencak, Vasil; Jeu, B.; Johannson, Herman; Juzl, Milos (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - "K": Kagan, Moisei S. (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - "K": Kagan, Moisei S. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - "K": Kalinnikov, L.A.; Kallas, Alla A.; Kanarskii, A.S.; Kandel, Boris L.; Kantor, Anatolii M.; Kantorovich, Vl.; Karp, Poel M.; Kartseva, E.N. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - "K": Kall, Toomas; Kalbe, Ruth; Kangilaski, Jaak; Kask, Karin; Kaup, Peeter; Kelder, Priit; Kenkmann, Paul; Kerner, Richard (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - "K": Kamenskaia, Viktoriia Al. (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - "K": Kartseva, E. N. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - "K": Keshudov, R.; Kashtaner, N.M.; Kedrov, B.M.; Kerro, Leo (Lev); Kings; Kintsans Vl.; Kissel, M.; Kisunko, V. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - "K": Khachikian, IA.I.; Khiutt, Vladimir, P. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - "K": Khaikin, Iakov Z. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - "K": Khristov, Dmitrii, Iv. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - "K": Kiffer, Rosemari; Klement, F.; Klivar, Miroslav; Kuhirt, Ullrich (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - "K": Kiiashchenko, N.; Klement, Aleksandr, A.; Klement, M.A.; Klenskii, Dm.; Klimova, Galina; Klimovitskii, Boleslav; Kogan, Vl.Z. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - "K": Kogan, L.N. (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - "K": Kogan, L.N.; Koprinarov, L.; Kozhinov, Vadim; Kozlovskii, IAkov A.; Korallov, Marlen; Kostyrchenko, G.V. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - "K": Kon, Igor S. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - "K": Kot, Samuel (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - "K": Kozina, Olesia (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - "K": Kravchenko, I.I.; Krasnukhin, Konstantin; Krestinskii, A.; Krivtsun, O.; Krupina, O.F. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - "K": Kriukovskii, N.I. (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - "K": Kriukovskii, N.I.; Kulikova, I.S.; Kumok, IA.; Kurchikov, Leonid; Kushkova, Anna; Kuhirt, U.; Klivar, M. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - "K": Kuklinkova, T.; Kule, Maija; Kundrik, Jozef; Kieffen, R. (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - "L": Laidmae, Virve-Ines; Laosson, M; Lauristin, Marju; Lebuhn, Jurgen; Lehmann, Gunter; Lias, Part; Lillemets, Aino; Liimets, Heino; Lill, Anne; Loch, Michael; Loit, T. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - "L": Laidmae, Virve-Ines (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - "L": Lang, Valter (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - "L": Larmin, Oleg V. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - "L": Lazurkin, IU.; Ladygina, Ariadna G.; Lapin, Iziaslav P.; Larmin, Oleg; Larkov, A.P.; Latynina, A.A.; Lebada, IU.A; Lebedev, A.A.; Lakshin, Vl.IA. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - "L": Levinshtein Viktor IU; Levchuk, Larisa T.; Lektorskii, V. A.; Leonteva E., Lilov, Aleksandr (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - "L": Limantov, Feliks [Shaft] (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - "L": Lin, Tsziiao; Lindin, Semen; Liorentsevich, Igor G.; Loiko, Olga; Lominadze, S.; Luk, A.N., Loch, M. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - "L": Liubarskii, IA.N.; Liubinskii, I.L.; Liubovskii, E.O.; Liusyi, A.P.; Lushchik, Ch.B. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - "L": Lominadze, Sergo V. (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - "L": Luk, Aleksandr N. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - "M": Magrits, Irina; Mathauser, Zdenek; Matjus, Ulo; Mihalikova, Lubomira; Mittelman, Moric; Muniz, Luiz A. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - "M": Magritz, Kurt (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - "M": Magritz, Kurt (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - "M": Magritz, Kurt and Irina (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - "M": Magritz, Kurt and Irina (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - "M": Magritz, Kurt and Irina (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - "M": Magritz, Irina (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - "M": Makarov, M.G.; Malakhov, Viktor A.; Malinina, Nina; Malyshev, I.V.; Manuilov, V.A.; Mankovskaia, N.B.; Markarian, E.S.; Markulan, IA.K. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - "M": Makhlina, Svetlana T. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - "M": Malakhov, I.Ia. (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - "M": Malevich, Oleg M. (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - "M": Malter, Rudolf (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - "M": Malter, Rudolf (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - "M": Mankovskaia, Nadezhda B. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - "M": Maseev, I.; Makhlina, S.T.; Mottus, H.; Molchanova, A.S.; Motyleva, T.L. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - "M": Mathauser, Z. (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - "M": Mazepa, V.I.; Meerovskii, B.V.; Meleshchenko, Z.N.; Mendelevich, E.; Mezhirov, A.; Mikushvich, V.B.; Milova, T.; Mikhailovskaia, Noemi M. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy A. (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy A. (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy A. (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy A. (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy A. (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy A. (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy A. (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy A. (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy A. (Box 94, Folders 7)
    - "M": Medvedev, Zhores A. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - "M": Medvedev, Zhores A. (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - "M": Medvedev, Zhores A. (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - "M": Medvedev, Zhores A. (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - "M": Medvedev, Zhores A. (Box 94, Folders 8)
    - "M": Medvedev, Zhores A. (Box 94, Folders 9)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - "M": Medvedev, Roy and Zhores, A. (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - "M": Meiner, Richard (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - "M": Meri, Lennart (Box 128, Folder 1)
      Meri, Lennart
    - "M": Mikhalev, V.; Molchanova, Albina; Moreva, Liuba M.; Motroshilova, Nelia V.; Motyleva, Tamara L.; Munipov, V.; Miasnikov, A.S.; Milinder, L.M. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - "M": Mikhailovskaia, N.M. (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - "M": Mikhalikova, Lubomira (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - "M": Morawski, Stefan (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - "M": Morawski, Stefan (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - "M": Moroshkina, Irina (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - "M": Muniz, Luis (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - "N": Naan, Gustav; Napinen, L. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - "N": Narskii, I.S.; Natev, A. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - "N": Novikov, V.; Novikova, V.I.; Nikolaev, I.V.; Nikiforov, B.; Neiding, V.L. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - "N": Novikova, Lidiia I. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - "O": Olt, Harry (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - "O": Olt, Harry (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - "O": Ovsiannikov, Mikhail F. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - "O": Ovsiannikov, M.F.; Ovchinnikov, Viktor F.; Okrainskii, IUlii; Opektsina, Tatiana; Orlov, Boris (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - "P": Palamets, Hillar; Park (Pork), Andrus; Partel, Aili; Piiper, J.; Plavius, Heinz; Poldmae, Asta; Prat, Naftali (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - "P": Pallo, Elena L.; Pankov, N.A.; Parsadanov, N. IA.; Parkhomovskii, Mikhail A.; Pasi, Isak (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - "P": Parolek, Radegast (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - "P": Peterajova, Ludmila (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - "P": Petritskii, V.; Petrovic, Sreten; Pechko, Leila P.; Pivoev, V.M.; Plotkin, A.B.; Peterajova, Ludmila (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - "P": Petrov, L.V. (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - "P": Petrovic, Sreten (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - "P": Plavius, Heinz (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - "P": Poliakov, A. P. (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - "P": Plotnikov, S.M.; Poliak, L.; Poliakov, A.P.; Poliakov, Mark IA.; Prazdnikov, G. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - "P": Prozhogin, N.P. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "P": Prozhogin, N.P. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "P": Prozhogin, N.P. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "P": Prozhogin, N.P. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "P": Prozhogin, N.P. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "P": Prozhogin, N.P. (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - "R": Ramler M.; Rahula, Maido; Redeker, H.; Randla, Alma (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - "R": Rappoport, Semen K. (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - "R": Raudar, Marina; Raskin, Arkadii I.; Rogov, Igor; Rudnev, P.A.; Ryvkina, Inna; Rashkovskii, E.B.; Rosner, K. (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - "R": Rebane, Jaan; Rehe, Erika; Ruger, Maria (Box 68, Folder 6)
      Rebane, Jaan Karl, 1924-; Wojnar, Irena
    - "R": Rehe, Erika (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - "R": Rondestvedt, Karen (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - "R": Ruuber, Georg E. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - "S": Saleev, V.A.; Samartsev, Anatolii I.; Sapozhnikov, G.M.; Selivanov, V.V.; Semenishcheva, Olga; Sergievskaia, IUliia, V. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - "S": Salizzoni, Roberto; Saluri, Rein; Sarap, Rudolf; Scanlan, James; Sasaki, Ken-Ichi; Sergeev, Mikhail (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - "S": Samartsev, Anatolii I. (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - "S": Sardak, Liudmila L. (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - "S": Selivanov, Valerii Vl. (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - "Sh": Shavinskaia, S.A.; Shestakov, V.P.; Shestakova, IU.; Shestinskii, Oleg; Shevchenko, Konstantin I.; Shevchenko, V.M. (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - "Sh": Shtoff, V.A.; Shisshin, A.F.; Shitov, Igor P.; Shudina, E.P. (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - "S": Seim, Juri (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - "S": Seim, Juri (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - "S": Sepanmaa, Yrjo (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - "S": Seve, Lucian; Seydevitz, Max; Sein, Hagi; Sepanmaa, Yrjo; Siiman, Evi; Siimei, Enn; Speiser, Erika; Stark, Werner (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - "S": Sigalov, M.S.; Sobolev, Petr V.; Skurzhin, M.; Skir, A.IA.; Sidorov, A.A. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - "S": Sinitskii, Anatolii N. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - "S": Skatershchikov, Viktor K. (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - "S": Skir, Aron IA. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - "S": Smolianinov, Ivan F. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - "S": Sozontov, Genadii M.; Sokolenko, V.M.; Solovev, E.IU.; Somov, Georgii IU.; Stafetskaia, Mara (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - "S": Stark, Werner (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - "S": Staudacher, Diana (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - "S": Staufenbiel, F.; Steila, Daniela; Steinberg, Valentin (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - "S": Stempel, Elvina; Straus, Tomas; Stromqvist, Sven; Sutrop, Margit; Swidorski, Edward; Sziklai, Laszlo (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - "S": Stoikov, Atanas; Stolovich, Imma-Mare; Stoshkus, K.; Stul, IA.E.; Syrkin, A.IA.; Sukhodolskii, V. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - "S": Straume, Mara (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - "S": Straume, Mara (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - "S": Symonovich, Valentin L. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - "S": Swedner, Harald (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - "T": Tamashan, L.G.; Takho-Godi, Elena; Tinkelman, Aron; Tipsin, N.N.; Trofimov, Pavel S.; Turkel (Boreba) Lina I.; Tamaru, IU., Tarasti, Eero (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - "T": Tselma, Elena M. (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - "T": Tszin, IAna (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - "T": Tsziio, Lin (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - "V": Vahemetsa, Aigar (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - "V": Vanslov, V.V. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "V": Vanslov, V.V. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - "U": Ugrinovich, D.; Usakina, T.; Uspenskaia, Tatiana; Uspenskii, B.A.; Ustiantsev, Vladimir, B.; Usychenko, Leonid; Uzelai, Milan (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - "U": Uibo, Kalju; Urbanova, Noima (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - "V": Vaart, Helgi; Vaga, V.; Valt, L.; Vaross, M. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - "V": Vaisman, Miron; Vanslov, V.V.; Vasilenko, V.A.; Veisblat, G.; Vekker, Lev M., Vereschagina, T. (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - "V": Vaross, M. (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - "V": Vazques, Adolfo Sanchez; Veidemann, Rein; Velliste, Trivimi; Vevere, V.; Vihalemm, Rein; Vinogradov, I.I. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - "V": Vidakovic, Mikhailo; Vidgof, V.M.; Vintsiunas, Vitautas; Voikhanskie, Mikhail amd Larisa; Voitashevskii (Elder), Aleksandr (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - "V": Visnap, Leili; Vooglaid, Ulo (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - "V": Volkov, V.I.; Volkova, El.; Vodzinskaia, Vera; Volovich, L.A.; Voronina, Nataliia Iv.; Volpert, L.I. (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - "W": Wojnar, Irena; Wolandt, Geid (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - "W": Wojnar, Irena (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - "W": Wolandt, Gerd (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - "Z": Zakharov, Nikolai P. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - "Z": Zambrovskii, B.Ia.; Zakharov, Efim Z.; Zakharov, N.P.; Zavadskaia, Evgeniia Vl. (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - "Z": Zaretskii, V. (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - "Z": Zis, Avner IA. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - "Z": Zelenov, Lev; Zelmanova, Evgeniia L.; Zolotareva, N.I.; Zolotov, Dmitrii; Zhovtis, A.L.; Zuradov, Armen; Zhuchkov, Vladimir Al. (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - "Z": Zweerde, E. van der (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Business and Professional Correspondence
    - Professional correspondence: Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Professional correspondence: Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Professional correspondence: Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Professional correspondence: Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Professional correspondence: Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Professional correspondence: Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Professional correspondence: Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Professional correspondence: Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Professional correspondence: Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence with publishing houses (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with editors (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with editors (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with editors (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with editors (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence with publishing houses: Publishing agreements (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with publishing houses: Publishing agreements (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with publishing houses and editors (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence with publishing house "Iskusstvo" (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with publishing house "Sovetskaia Entsiklopediia" (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Requests to purchase periodicals in various languages for Faculty of Philosophy, Tartu University (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Series 3. Creative works
  - Poetry (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Poetry (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Poetry (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Poetry: Published (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Poetry: Unpublished (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Poetry: Reviews (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Poetry: Reviews (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Poems dedicated to Stolovich (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Translations by Stolovich: Valmar Adams (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Notebooks with early poems, 1930s-1940s (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Notebooks with early poems, 1940s (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Notebooks with early poems, 1941-1943 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Notebooks with early poems and occasional drawings, 1942-1944 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Drafts and notes (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - "O poniatii 'Tip khudozhestvennogo tvorchestva' ", 1974, 1976, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Articles and reviews, 1982, 1985, 1994, 1997-1998, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Kultura khudozhestvennaia i kultura esteticheskaia", n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Gnoseologicheskie i aksiologicheskie aspekty iskusstvoznaniia", 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - " Esteticheskie vzgliady K. Marksa i F. Engelsa", 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "On the concept of 'Axiosphere'", 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Kategoriia prekrasnogo i obshchestvennyi ideal", 1969: Proofreading (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "The systemic pluralism of A.F. Losev's philosophy", 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Rol fotografii v transliatsii, fiksatsii i sozdanii tsennostei" (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Filosofiia krasoty", 1976: Typescript (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - "Filosofiia krasoty", 1976: Typescript (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - "Filosofiia krasoty", 1976: Reviews (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - "Iskusstvo i svobodnoe vremia" (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "Khudozhestvennaia deiatelnost kak subektno-obektnoe otnoshenie" (Box 13, Folders 5)
  - "Aksiologiia Peterburga" (Box 13, Folders 6)
  - "Spory o sudbakh iskusstva": Materials (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - "Spory o sudbakh iskusstva": Materials (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - "Zerkalo kak semioticheskaia, gnoseologicheskaia i aksiologicheskaia model" (Box 13, Folders 7)
  - "Po esteticheskomu vospitaniiu" (Box 13, Folders 8)
  - "Tsennosti sotsialnogo gumanizma" (Box 13, Folders 9)
  - "IUmor avtorskii i anonimskii" (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - "IUmor avtorskii i anonimskii" (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - "Evrei shutiat": Materials for the book (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - "Evrei shutiat": Materials for the book (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - "Evrei shutiat": Card Index (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 1st ed: Card Index (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 1st ed: Card Index (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 1st ed: Card Index (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 1st ed: Materials for the book (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 1st ed: Proof-pages (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 1st ed: Proof-pages (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 2nd ed., 1996 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 2nd ed., 1996 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 2nd ed., 1996: Supplemental materials (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 3rd ed., 1999 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 3rd ed., 1996: Supplemental materials (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 3rd ed., 1996: Supplemental materials (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 4th ed., 2002: Proof-pages (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 4th ed., 2002: Proof-pages (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 4th ed., 2002: Supplemental materials (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - "Evrei shutiat", 4th ed., 2002: Supplemental materials (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - "Evrei shutiat": Typescipt and additional materials (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - "Evrei shutiat": Reviews, correspondence (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - "Evrei shutiat": Reviews (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - "Evrei shutiat": Publishing agreements (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Aesthetics: notes (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Aesthetics: notes, summaries, lesson plans (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Aesthetics: notes, summaries, lesson plans (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Aesthetics: notes, summaries, lesson plans (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Aesthetics: notes, summaries, lesson plans (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Aesthetics: Bibliography (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - "Priroda i funktsii esteticheskogo": kollektivnaia monografiia, 1968 (Box 145, Folder 2)